Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is dirt cake topped. Let me show
you how to make it. In a Ninja Creamy
Pint, you're going to combine 400 g of a
fat-free high protein milk, a little bit
of vanilla bean paste, some sweetener,
salt, zantham gum, jello pudding mix,
and we're going to blend that all up and
throw it in the freezer for at least 16
hours. Once it's nice and frozen, you
can take it out, run under hot water for
about a minute, and then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. It's probably going to be a
little powdery, so this is going to need
a respin. But before you do that, you
can just scrape down the sides with a
butter knife. This will help get some of
those ice crystals off of the sides. And
then, depending on how close your creamy
is to being done, you can hollow a hole
in the center and fill it with three
Oreo thins with the cream removed. If
you guys didn't know, the cream is about
15 of the 35 calories in an Oreo thin.
And I don't know about you, but the only
part of nori you can taste in ice cream
is the cookie part. So, I just go with
that. And then we're going to top it
with some sugar-free chocolate sauce. I
got this one from Lanto. It is 10 times
better than any of the ones I've tried
before. The Hershey's one specifically.
[__] you. That one sucked. And then you
can just top it with one final Oreo
thin. Shake that around and you're good
to go. Comment which Ben & Jerry's
flavor you want me to recreate next.
I'll do the most like comment.